* FAQs

[Home](https://www.livelydirect.com/ "Go to Lively.")\>Privacy Policy

Lively Direct Privacy Policy
============================

The Lively flip cell phone and medical alert are sold by Journey Health & Lifestyle™, formerly known as firstSTREET. At Journey Health & Lifestyle™, we understand that the protection of consumers’ privacy is an important public concern. Accordingly, we have adopted this Privacy Statement to serve as the foundation for our internal privacy policies and procedures. It is our commitment to providing meaningful privacy protection for our customers.

1\. Email
---------

By supplying us with your email address you will receive order confirmation notices, exclusive offers only available through email and product updates. Journey Health & Lifestyle™ will not sell or rent your email address and we respect your online privacy. If you do not wish to receive such mailings, please let us know by sending an email to us at [\[email protected\]](https://www.livelydirect.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection), or by calling Journey Health & Lifestyle™ Customer Service at [1-800-704-1209](tel:18007041209) between 9:00 AM and 8:00 PM ET Monday – Friday. You can expect to receive a response from Journey Health & Lifestyle™ within 24 hours (Monday through Friday) of sending your email. If you have any questions or concerns, you can also email us at [\[email protected\]](https://www.livelydirect.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

2\. Information security
------------------------

We maintain technical and organizational safeguards to protect the confidentiality of personal information about our customers against unauthorized access or disclosure, accidental loss, alteration or destruction.

3\. Information Quality
-----------------------

We maintain procedures to assure that the personal information we collect is accurate, up-to-date and as complete as possible. If we obtain information about individuals who are not our present customers, we strive to treat this information in the same manner as we treat information about our existing customers.

4\. Use of Customer Information
-------------------------------

We collect personal information from our customers themselves, from when we provide products or services to our customers and from consumer reporting agencies and outside sources. We use personal information only for purposes of administering our business activities, providing service and making available other products and services to our present and prospective customers.

The personal information that our customers give us, and information about our customers’ orders may be shared with third parties. These marketing partners may use this information to send our customers offers of interest.

We use third parties to improve our ability to identify visitors to our website. As part of this service, we may make available identifiers to these third parties including our visitors’ IP addresses, cookies, and hashed versions of email addresses captured from your visit. We, and third parties, use this data to obtain more information about our visitors and reach out to them through other channels, such as email and/or direct mail. You have the right to opt-out of this activity.

5\. Do Not Solicit Option
-------------------------

We recognize that some of our customers do not want to be solicited for offers and promotions from us. So, we provide our customers the option to have their names and addresses removed from our mail and/or telephone solicitation lists. We have procedures that assure a consumer’s name, address and telephone number are removed from our marketing lists.

Customers that do not want us to contact them can let us know by calling, writing, or sending an email to us at [\[email protected\]](https://www.livelydirect.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection). Customers that do not want us to share their name and addresses with third party marketing partners can let us know by sending an email to us at [\[email protected\]](https://www.livelydirect.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

6\. Maintaining Customer Privacy with Our Business Partners
-----------------------------------------------------------

We strive to ensure that the companies we use as our business partners support our commitment to privacy protection in their handling of personal data about our customers.

7\. Employee Education
----------------------

We provide training to our employees about their responsibilities under this Privacy Statement, and we expect them to do their parts in protecting our customers’ privacy. We also conduct regular internal audits to support our commitment.

8\. Privacy Statement Availability to Customers
-----------------------------------------------

We want our customers to know about our commitment to providing privacy protection. Therefore, this Privacy Statement is available upon request to customers, investors, employees, governmental authorities and members of the general public.

### Company

* **Visit Our New Main Store:**  

### Support

### Get In Touch

* **For Jitterbug Flip2 Call:**  
* **For Lively Mobile2 Call:**  
* **For Jitterbug Smart4 Call:**  

© 2023 Journey Health & Lifestyle™, Virginia, United States.

(formerly firstSTREET for Boomers and Beyond, Inc.)

We will refund the full price of the Jitterbug Flip2 phone and the activation fee, if any, if it is returned within 30 days of purchase in like-new condition. We will also refund your first monthly service charge if you have used less than 30 minutes of talk and less that 50 text messages. Per minute and per text charges otherwise apply. You will be charged a $10 restocking fee. Shipping charges are not refundable. Full terms at [www.lively.com/legal/guarantee](https://www.lively.com/legal/guarantee).

\*$5/mo. discount when you enroll in paperless billing. Full price $24.99/mo., plus taxes and fees. Monthly fees do not include government taxes or fees and are subject to change. A data plan is required for the Jitterbug Smart. Plans and services may require purchase of a Lively device and one-time activation fee of $35. Pricing may vary. For details on current pricing, visit lively.com. Not all Lively services are available on all plans. See plans for details. See lively.com/link for details. Urgent Response, Nurse On-Call, and Ask Lively’s Operator Services available 24/7. Customer Service and Care Advocate available during normal business hours. Urgent Response or 911 calls can be made only when cellular service is available. Coverage is not available everywhere. Urgent Response tracks an approx. location of device when device is turned on and connected to the network. Lively does not guarantee an exact location. Lively is not a healthcare provider. Nurse On-Call provides registered nurses who evaluate medical urgency, provide symptom management or health information, transfer to a physician if appropriate and schedule appointments. Physician transfer at discretion of the nurse. Emergencies will be transferred to a 911 call center, or members may be directed to call 911. In the event physician services are not available, the nurse may suggest you contact your primary care physician or visit your local Urgent Care. See terms for details. Lively does not provide transportation services. Lively partners with Lyft, Inc. which operates a ridesharing platform (“Lyft Platform”). Ride fares are applied to your monthly Lively bill. Minutes will be deducted from your rate plan. Lively is not liable for any act or omission, including negligence, by Lyft or its drivers. See terms and conditions at www.lively.com. Porting is dependent on the availability of the phone number requested and subject to approval of the existing carrier. Consistently rated fast and reliable by IHS Markit’s RootScore Reports. By enabling Alexa on the Jitterbug Flip2, you acknowledge that Lively is not responsible for Amazon Alexa’s functionality or services. Other marks are property of their respective owners and may be trademarks. Screen images simulated. Appearance of device may vary. Lively and Jitterbug are trademarks of Best Buy Health, Inc. ©2023 Best Buy. All rights reserved.

Specifications listed are approximates and not always exact, & may be subject to change. Newer features may not be available on older production models.

The information contained in this website is subject to change without notice.

WE TAKE YOUR SECURITY SERIOUSLY

This site is https secured. By using this site and/or by ordering on this site you agree to our [Privacy Policy](https://www.livelydirect.com/privacy-policy/), [Terms & Conditions](https://www.livelydirect.com/terms-conditions/), as posted on this site.
